export const chapter = "Chapter - 6: Nouns : Gender ";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
        {
          question: "What does Masculine Gender represent?",
          optionA: "Male Nouns",
          optionB: "Female Nouns",
          optionC: "Both male and female Nouns",
          correctAnswer: "Male Nouns",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which of the following pairs represent Masculine and Feminine genders, respectively?",
          optionA: "Cock, Hen",
          optionB: "Brother, Sister",
          optionC: "Actor, Actress",
          correctAnswer: "Actor, Actress",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which gender category includes nouns like doctor and teacher?",
          optionA: "Masculine Gender",
          optionB: "Feminine Gender",
          optionC: "Common Gender",
          correctAnswer: "Common Gender",
        },
        {
          question: "What does Neuter Gender represent?",
          optionA: "Male Nouns",
          optionB: "Female Nouns",
          optionC: "Lifeless Objects",
          correctAnswer: "Lifeless Objects",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which of the following pairs represent Common Gender nouns?",
          optionA: "Hunter, Huntress",
          optionB: "Parent, Patient",
          optionC: "Lion, Lioness",
          correctAnswer: "Parent, Patient",
        },
        {
          question: "What kind of gender represents nouns like aunt and niece?",
          optionA: "Feminine Gender",
          optionB: "Masculine Gender",
          optionC: "Common Gender",
          correctAnswer: "Feminine Gender",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which category includes nouns that can be either male or female?",
          optionA: "Masculine Gender",
          optionB: "Feminine Gender",
          optionC: "Common Gender",
          correctAnswer: "Common Gender",
        },
        {
          question: "Which of the following represent Neuter Gender nouns?",
          optionA: "Dog, Bitch",
          optionB: "Car, Coat",
          optionC: "Brother, Sister",
          correctAnswer: "Car, Coat",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is the gender category of nouns like friend and guest?",
          optionA: "Masculine Gender",
          optionB: "Feminine Gender",
          optionC: "Common Gender",
          correctAnswer: "Common Gender",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What kind of gender represents nouns such as grandfather and grandmother?",
          optionA: "Masculine Gender",
          optionB: "Feminine Gender",
          optionC: "Common Gender",
          correctAnswer: "Masculine Gender",
        },
      ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blank with correct option:",
    questions: [
        {
          question: "Masculine Gender represents nouns that denote __________.",
          optionA: "Female entities",
          optionB: "Male entities",
          optionC: "Inanimate objects",
          correctAnswer: "Male entities",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Feminine Gender category includes words portraying __________.",
          optionA: "Male figures",
          optionB: "Female figures",
          optionC: "Both genders equally",
          correctAnswer: "Female figures",
        },
        {
          question: "Common Gender nouns can refer to __________.",
          optionA: "Only male entities",
          optionB: "Both male and female entities",
          optionC: "Inanimate objects",
          correctAnswer: "Both male and female entities",
        },
        {
          question: "Neuter Gender encompasses __________.",
          optionA: "Male and female entities",
          optionB: "Inanimate objects",
          optionC: "Only living beings",
          correctAnswer: "Inanimate objects",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The word 'niece' falls under the __________ gender category.",
          optionA: "Masculine",
          optionB: "Feminine",
          optionC: "Common",
          correctAnswer: "Feminine",
        },
        {
          question:
            "A noun categorized under the Common Gender can denote __________.",
          optionA: "Only male beings",
          optionB: "Both male and female beings",
          optionC: "Inanimate things",
          correctAnswer: "Both male and female beings",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Masculine Gender represents words that signify __________.",
          optionA: "Female beings exclusively",
          optionB: "Male beings exclusively",
          optionC: "Inanimate objects",
          correctAnswer: "Male beings exclusively",
        },
        {
          question: "The word 'grandmother' belongs to the __________ gender.",
          optionA: "Masculine",
          optionB: "Feminine",
          optionC: "Common",
          correctAnswer: "Feminine",
        },
        {
          question: "Neuter Gender encompasses nouns representing __________.",
          optionA: "Male figures",
          optionB: "Female figures",
          optionC: "Lifeless objects",
          correctAnswer: "Lifeless objects",
        },
        {
          question: "Common Gender includes words that can denote __________.",
          optionA: "Only male beings",
          optionB: "Both male and female beings",
          optionC: "Only female beings",
          correctAnswer: "Both male and female beings",
        },
      ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
        {
          question:
            "In order to start Tux Paint in windowed mode, clicking on the Tux Paint (Windowed) in the Tux Paint folder is necessary.",
          optionA: "Correct",
          optionB: "Incorrect",
          correctAnswer: "Correct",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Shapes tool in Tux Paint is primarily used for pasting images into drawings.",
          optionA: "Correct",
          optionB: "Incorrect",
          correctAnswer: "Incorrect",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Text tool in Tux Paint is capable of drawing simple shapes.",
          optionA: "Correct",
          optionB: "Incorrect",
          correctAnswer: "Incorrect",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Eraser tool in Tux Paint is used for adding special effects to drawings.",
          optionA: "Correct",
          optionB: "Incorrect",
          correctAnswer: "Incorrect",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The 'Undo' button in Tux Paint repeats the last drawing action.",
          optionA: "Correct",
          optionB: "Incorrect",
          correctAnswer: "Incorrect",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The 'Redo' button in Tux Paint cancels the last drawing action.",
          optionA: "Correct",
          optionB: "Incorrect",
          correctAnswer: "Incorrect",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Clicking 'Save' in Tux Paint directly saves the current drawing without any prompts.",
          optionA: "Correct",
          optionB: "Incorrect",
          correctAnswer: "Correct",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The 'Open' button in Tux Paint is solely used to close the current drawing.",
          optionA: "Correct",
          optionB: "Incorrect",
          correctAnswer: "Incorrect",
        },
        {
          question: "The Magic tool in Tux Paint erases drawings.",
          optionA: "Correct",
          optionB: "Incorrect",
          correctAnswer: "Incorrect",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Members of a family usually don't celebrate festivals, birthdays, or special occasions together.",
          optionA: "Correct",
          optionB: "Incorrect",
          correctAnswer: "Incorrect",
        },
      ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
